A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 7: Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Files, 1957-2005
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Clippings on Issues (Includes proposals for a toll road and on sound barriers), 1980-1990 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Widening Proposals, 1990, 2000-2002 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Email Correspondence, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-270 (Maryland), 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-395 (and HOV Lanes), 1979-1988 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-495 (Capital Beltway), 1985-1999 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-495 (Capital Beltway) - Conference on the Capital Beltway, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - Proposed Outer Beltway/Western Bypass, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Parkways - George Washington Memorial Parkway, 1975-1986 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Rt. 1 (Richmond Highway), Undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Rt. 29 (Lee Highway) and Nutley Street Area (Fairlee/Metro West); Virginia Center Proposal, 1981-2004 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission. Highway Allocation Workshops, Undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation. Final Allocation of Interstate, Primary and Urban Construction Funds FY1979-1980 (Revised); FY1980-1981, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 7 (Leesburg Pike), 1972-1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 28 (Sully Road), 1987 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 123 (Chain Bridge Road) - Intersection at International Drive at Tysons Corner; map International Drive to I-495, 1977-1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 123 (Chain Bridge Road) - Intersection with Rt. 267 (Dulles Access Road and Toll Road), 1985, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 123 - Intersection with Old Dominion Drive, 1962-1989 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 193 (Georgetown Pike), 1972-1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 193 (Georgetown Pike) - Accidents, 1979-1991 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 193 (Georgetown Pike) - Historic Overlay District, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 193 (Georgetown Pike) - Mesmer Rezoning Case (RZ 80-D-079), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 193 (Georgetown Pike) - VDHT Study Report (2 copies), 1978? (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - General Material and Correspondence on Transit Planning in the Dulles Access Road Corridor, 1974-2000 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - A Mass Transit Plan for the Tysons/Dulles Corridor, 1990 December (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Carpool Access, 1976-1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Committee for Dulles, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Development of Traffic Management Strategies for the Dulles International Airport Access Highway (Final Report - Phase 2), 1981 March (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Dulles Airport Access Road Corridor Study, 1978 July (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Dulles Corridor Plan (Draft), 1992 January (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Express Bus System, 1986-2002 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Express Bus System. HTNB …Development of Immediate Action Program…, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Extension Inside the Beltway (Dulles Connector; Tysons Bypass), 1978-1981 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Extension Inside the Beltway - Proposal Study: Dulles Access Highway Extension…, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Extension Inside the Beltway - Preliminary Design Report, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Extension Inside the Beltway - Final Environmental Impact Statement (Copy 1), 1980 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Extension Inside the Beltway - Final Environmental Impact Statement (Copy 2), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Loudoun County Transportation Considerations, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Metro Extension, 1980-2005 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1988 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Noise Studies, 1981-1992 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Park and Ride Lots; Dartrail Proposal, 1988-1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes (1 of 3), 1973-1989 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes (2 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes (3 of 3), 1979-1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - Dulles Airport Access Road Outer Parallel Toll Roads (Combined Location-Design Public Hearing Summary Report), 1981 May (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - Dulles Airport Access Road Outer Parallel Toll Roads (Draft Environmental Impact Statement), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - JHK Associates. Dulles Toll Road Study (Final Report), 1979 January (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - Dulles Toll Road Widening Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - JHK Associates. Feasibility of the Dulles Toll Road, 1978 November (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Toll Lanes/Parallel Lanes - Testimony of Lilla Richards before the Commonwealth Transportation Board, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - UMTA. Grant for Dulles Access Mass Transit (1 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - UMTA. Grant for Dulles Access Mass Transit (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - UMTA. Grant for Dulles Access Mass Transit (3 of 3), 1989-1991 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 267 (Dulles Airport Access Road and Dulles Access Toll Road) - Wolftrap Fringe Parking, 1973-1984 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 286 (formerly Rt. 7100) (Fairfax County Parkway; formerly called the Springfield Bypass), 1979-1991 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 309/738 (Old Dominion Drive), 1981-1986 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers, 1973-1977 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers and Member Lists, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean Planning Committee - Chain Bridge Road Committee Papers, 1983, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - Intersection with Rt. 309 (Old Dominion Drive), 1981 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - "Transportation Study Report" (by VDHT) (2 copies), 1978 May (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - "Environmental Assessment" (by VDHT), 1981(?) (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - "Chain Bridge Road Area Transportation Study Report" (by VDHT), 1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - Intersection with Rt. 309 (Old Dominion Drive) - "Location & Design Study Report", ca. 1980 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - Intersection with Rt. 309 (Old Dominion Drive) - Proposed Roundabout, Pt. 1 (McLean Revitalization Corporation Papers), 2001 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - Intersection with Rt. 309 (Old Dominion Drive) - Proposed Roundabout, Pt. 2 (McLean Revitalization Corporation Papers), 2001 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Virginia - State Highways - Rt. 3547 (Chain Bridge Road and Old Chain Bridge Road) - McLean CBD - Intersection with Rt. 309 (Old Dominion Drive) - Proposed Roundabout, Pt. 3 (McLean Revitalization Corporation Papers), 1997-2002 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia - Bureau of Social Science Research, Inc. Selected Findings: Northern Virginia Survey of Attitudes of Transportation Issues and Alternatives, 1979 March (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Fairfax County - General Materials, 1973, 1978, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Bond Issues, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Algonkian Parkway (formerly Holly Knolls Road) and Thomas Avenue; Dranesville Road, 1979-1988 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Arnon Chapel Road, Great Falls, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Balls Hill Road, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Brook Road, McLean, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Dranesville District - Spot Safety Improvements and Intersection Studies, 1978-1988 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Elm Street - McLean Central Business District - Building Heights, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Widening Controversy, 1971-1977 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Widening Controversy, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Widening Controversy (Part 1 of 2), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Widening Controversy (Part 2 of 2), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Widening Controversy, 1979-1981 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Great Falls Street - Lilla Richard's "Blue Notebook" on Great Falls Street and West Falls Church Metro Station Accessibility, 1978-1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Haycock Road, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Herndon Parkway, 1987-1991 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Idylwood Road - Realignment with Kirby Road Intersection (Rezoning application 79-D-103, Theron L. and Gloria C. Dikeman), 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Kirby Road Bridge, 1977-1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Lemon Road, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Spring Hill Road Interchange with Rt. 267 (Dulles Access Road); Signal at Old Dominion Drive, 1978-1988 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Westmoreland Street, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Wiehle Avenue and vicinity in Herndon, 1988-1991 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Roads - Fairfax County - Streets - Winter Hunt and Old Falls Streets (Street Vacation), 1983 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Series 8: Elections Files, 1971-1991
  - Sub-Series 8-1: Local Election and Political Topics Files, 1971-1991
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1975 Election, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1975 Election Results in Dranesville District, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1979 Election Results, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1981 Election, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1982 Election, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - Special Task Force on Voluntary Campaign Guidelines and Land Use Disclosure Papers and Report (Part 1), 1982 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - Special Task Force on Voluntary Campaign Guidelines and Land Use Disclosure Papers and Report (Part 2), 1982 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1983 Fairfax County Supervisor Election, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1984-1985 Democratic Political Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 10th District Democratic Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1986 Election, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - Fairfax County Democratic Election Manuals, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1987 Election, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - 1989 Election, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Files on Earlier Elections and Political Topics - Election Results, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Lilla Richards' File on John T. (Til) Hazel (1930- ), 1971-1986 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Lilla Richards' File on J. Hamilton Lambert (1940- ), 1990-1991 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Lilla Richards' File on Audrey Moore (1928-2018), 1982-1991 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Lilla Richards' File on Audrey Moore (1928-2018) - Lawsuit against John T. Hazel, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Lilla Richards' File on John P. Shacochis (1915-2004), 1975-1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Lilla Richards' File on Robert L. Thoburn (1929-2012), 1987-1990 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 8-2: Lilla Richards 1987 and 1991 Campaigns, 1987-1991
    - Lilla Richards' Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor, Dranesville District (Includes a copy of The Richards Record, vol. 1, no. 1), 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Lilla Richards' Binder of basic topical information and pamphlets for citizens on Fairfax County government and services (part 1), 1990 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Lilla Richards' Binder of basic topical information and pamphlets for citizens on Fairfax County government and services (part 2), 1990 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Lilla Richards' Binder of basic topical information and pamphlets for citizens on Fairfax County government and services (part 3), 1990 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Lilla Richards Reelection Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor, Dranesville District - Financial Papers, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Lilla Richards Reelection Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor, Dranesville District - Financial Papers, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Lilla Richards Reelection Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor, Dranesville District - Financial Papers, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Lilla Richards Reelection Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor - Subject Binder on Campaign Issues, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Lilla Richards Reelection Campaign for Fairfax County Supervisor - Subject Binder - Loose Papers, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 1991 Campaign Issue - Lawn Mowing and Weed Ordinance, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Ernest J. Berger 1991 Campaign Material, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 1991 General Election Materials, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Series 9: Organizations Files, 1973-2016
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Consumer Congress, 1978-1981 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100, 1977-1982 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1980 Board Meetings, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1980 Newsletters, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1981 Board Meetings, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1981 Newsletters, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1982 Newsletters, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1983 Newsletters, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1984 Newsletters, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1985 Newsletters, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1986 Newsletters, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1987 Newsletters, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Committee of 100 - 1999, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Fairfax County Taxpayers Alliance, 1977-1981 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Forward Fairfax - Newsletter, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - The League of Women Voters, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - The League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area - League Bulletins, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - The League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area - Transportation Studies and Papers, 1980-1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Managed Home Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Marriott Corporation (Gino's/Roy Rogers), 1982, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - McLean Business and Professional Association - McLean Villager Newsletter, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Lilla Richard's Files on Organizations - McLean Teen Center [photographs], 1987-2016 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - National Organization for Women, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Lilla Richard's Files on Organizations - Sharon Masonic Lodge, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Lilla Richard's Files on Organizations - Virginia Commission on the Arts, 1978-1980 (Box 85, Folder 13)